×

Loading...

×

Loading...

×

Loading...

### ItemFix Privacy Policy (last update December 2021)

### Common ID Cookie

This site uses cookies and similar tracking technologies such as the Common ID cookie to provide its services. Cookies are important devices for measuring advertising effectiveness and ensuring a robust online advertising industry. The Common ID cookie stores a unique user id in the first party domain and is accessible to our ad partners. This simple ID that can be utilized to improve user matching, especially for delivering ads to iOS and MacOS browsers. Users can opt out of the Common ID tracking cookie by clicking [here](#opt-out).

### Advertising Privacy Settings

FOR EU USERS ONLY: When you use our site, pre-selected companies may access and use certain information on your device and about your interests to serve ads or personalized content. You may revisit or change consent-choices at any time by clicking [here](#cmp).

Protecting the privacy of all of our users is an ongoing commitment of ItemFix.com services (hereinafter, "ItemFix"). This Privacy Policy, which applies to all websites and services provided under the ItemFix names and marks, explains how ItemFix treats personal information that we collect and receive. Personal information is information about you, not otherwise publicly available, that personally identifies you; personal information may include your name, location, e-mail address, birth date, or other identifying information.

ItemFix has established registration and sign-in procedures which, in conjunction with this Privacy Policy, help ensure the privacy of information provided to ItemFix by its visitors and members while using the ItemFix website. You should be aware that this Privacy Policy applies only to the ItemFix website and services, and not to any other websites you may visit before or after the ItemFix site.

Questions regarding our privacy policy should be directed [here](https://www.itemfix.com/contact_us).

**What Does the ItemFix Privacy Policy Cover?**

This privacy policy applies to web pages ending in ItemFix.com that contain a link to this privacy policy at the bottom of the web page. Inclusion of the ItemFix logo at the top of a web page does not necessarily mean that this privacy policy applies. Be sure to check the URL that you link to from ItemFix web pages to determine whether this privacy policy applies. If you have any questions about this, [contact us](https://www.itemfix.com/contact_us).

**What Information Does ItemFix Collect From You?**

You can visit our site and use most of our services without having to tell us who you are or reveal any personally identifiable information to us. There are, however, a few instances where we do collect personally identifiable information in order to fulfill your request.  
  
Whenever you visit ItemFix, our web server logs automatically receive and record information from your web browser including your IP Address, User Agent, ItemFix cookie information, the ItemFix page(s) you request, the time spent on each web page and any search terms you query.  
  
ItemFix uses this information to customize your experience on our site, to show you more relevant advertising messages, and to improve our services in general. This information allows other users to benefit from the quality searches you perform, ultimately receiving the most relevant, pertinent information.

When you register to become a Member of the ItemFix website, ItemFix collects certain information such as your e-mail address, your ip address, your user agent and your user name (collectively, "Membership Information").

ItemFix will not distribute, sell or rent any of the personal information about you to other people or nonaffiliated companies except to enable the provision of services or products you have requested or when we have your permission to do so.

Please remember that any personal information voluntarily disclosed by you that you choose to share is done within your sole discretion and we are not responsible for the outcome of that information. We encourage you to always remain aware of this possibility. ItemFix encourages you to use common sense and be cautious about what information you may provide on-line, whether through our websites or elsewhere on the Internet.

You acknowledge, consent, and agree that ItemFix may access, preserve, use, and disclose your Membership Information, including content uploaded to or downloaded from Itemfix websites and services, if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

Enforce the ItemFix Terms of Service;  
(b) Respond to claims that any uploaded materials violate the rights of third-parties;  
(c) Respond to your customer service requests;  
(d) Comply with legal process; and/or  
(e) Protect the rights, property, or personal safety of ItemFix, its users, or the public.

**How Do We Use Personal Information?**  
Our primary goal is to provide members with the most useful and enjoyable experience on the Internet. Our advertisers will never be privy to your Membership Information, unless you permit us to give it to them so that they can provide you with products or services. Your e-mail address may be used by us for communications related to the ItemFix services, including but not limited to sending notices about new features, products, or other information of interest to you.

The ItemFix website is constantly evolving and changing in content and in features. Member Information helps guide such changes and the evolution of our websites. Our advertisers and affiliates may be provided general information or data regarding membership usage patterns or interests, so that they too can better serve your needs and preferences, but such disclosure will not include individually identifiable information. The collection of usage and interest information allows us to provide a constantly evolving and user-sensitive package of services, products, and features that satisfy member needs, wants and desires but always with the priority of protecting individual member privacy.

**Do Any Third Parties Receive or Collect Your Information Through ItemFix?**

In the few instances where ItemFix collects personally identifiable information, ItemFix will not share it with other companies or individuals unless:

We have your permission to share the information; or

We need to share your information with certain third parties with which we have a business relationship in order to provide a product or service.

We are responding to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or-

If ItemFix is acquired by another company whether through merger or purchase of its stock or all or substantially all of its assets, we will share the information with the acquiring company.

Furthermore, ItemFix will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable information as customer lists to anyone. Nor will we share with anyone personally identifiable information about you that is of medical, financial or sexual nature.

ItemFix shares some of the user information, such as user trends, search language, and time of day with third parties that may set and access cookies on your computer. Other advertisers or advertising services may set cookies but this information is not shared with ItemFix nor is it personally identifiable information.

None if these third parties nor any other advertiser or advertising service, receives personally identifiable information from ItemFix. However, certain advertisements or contests you see on our site may provide for the collection of personally identifiable information. Such information is never shared with ItemFix.

You may adjust your computer’s web browser settings to refuse all cookies. However, please note that because cookies are widely used, disabling the use of cookies in your web browser may interfere with full use of various websites.

**Updates to this Privacy Policy**

ItemFix updates this policy from time to time. ItemFix reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of Itemfix following any amendment of the Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised policy terms. Bear in mind that the only way to ensure your personal privacy whenever you are on the Internet is to make sure your browser is configured so that you are alerted to all cookies.

**Cookies  
**ItemFix places cookies on your computer to retain your individual preferences and improve your user experience on our website, as well as to tell us what features of our sites are most popular.

Affiliates and advertisers, product and service providers may also use their own cookies when you interact with their sites and you should be aware of this as you do so.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies please follow the privacy links for the various companies below.

**How Do I Edit My Membership Information?  
**All of your Membership Information is located in your personal ItemFix profile. Your profile can be edited at any time, by logging in with your User Name and password, then clicking on the "Settings" link.

**Notice Regarding Children  
**We at ItemFix take the online safety of children very seriously. ItemFix websites and services are directed to adults. We do not allow children under the age of 13 to obtain User Names, and we do not intentionally collect any personal information from children under 13. If you are between the ages of 13-18 years old, we encourage you to discuss the use of this website with your parents.

**Third party advertisers**

Our advertisers have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policies below.

**COOKIES**

|     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Name** | **Domain** | **Function** | **Party** | **Class** | **Type** | **Expiry** |
|     |     |     |     |     |     |     |
| itemfix\_data | [itemfix.com](https://www.itemfix.com/privacy) | hashed string containing the following preferences:  <br>\* preferred comment sorting  <br>\* your user token  <br>\* language selection  <br>\* css theme preference | First | Personalization | Persistent | 1 year |
| \_ga | [Google analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy?gl=GB&hl=en) | Used to distinguish users. |     |     |     | 2 years |
| \_gid | [Google analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy?gl=GB&hl=en) | Used to distinguish users. |     |     |     | 24 hours |
| \_gat | [Google analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy?gl=GB&hl=en) | Used to throttle request rate. |     |     |     | 1 minute |
| AMP\_TOKEN | [Google analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy?gl=GB&hl=en) | Contains a token that can be used to retrieve a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. Other possible values indicate opt-out, inflight request or an error retrieving a Client ID from AMP Client ID service. |     |     |     | 30 seconds to 1 year |
| \_gac\_xxxx | [Google analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy?gl=GB&hl=en) | Contains campaign related information for the user. If you have linked your Google Analytics and AdWords accounts, AdWords website conversion tags will read this cookie unless you opt-out. |     |     |     | 90 days |
| ANON\_ID | [Tribalfusion.com](http://exponential.com/privacy/) | the anonymous hashed id in the cookie links the web user's browser to a profile which contains the behaviors the user has displayed | Third | Tracking | Persistent | 3 months |

**  
Legal Bases for processing your data**  
Legitimate Interests: We process some of your data because it is in our Legitimate Interests to do so. Where this is the case, we have considered the impact using your information may have on you, and limited our use to only what is strictly necessary.

**

How can you exercise your rights under the GDPR

**

· Access: If you wish to exercise your right to access a free copy of your data, you can contact us by clicking [this link](https://www.itemfix.com/contact_us).

· Deletion: To ask us to delete your data, please [contact us](https://www.itemfix.com/contact_us). However, there may be circumstances where we are legally entitled to retain it.

· Updating: If you wish to update your data, you can do this directly by editing your user settings.

· Objection to legitimate interests: If you wish to object to our processing of your data where we are pursuing our legitimate interests or those of a third party please [contact us](https://www.itemfix.com/contact_us).

If you are contacting us to exercise any of your rights under the GDPR, you will have to provide valid proof of identification. We are required to respond to your request within 1 month.

**

Governing Law and Jurisdiction

**This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Belgium. You agree that any dispute arising from or relating to the privacy policy shall be governed by the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Belgium.

**Your Questions or Suggestions Regarding this Privacy Policy.**

If you have a privacy concern regarding any ItemFix website or this Policy, and if you cannot satisfactorily resolve it through the use of the websites, you should [contact us here](https://www.itemfix.com/contact_us)

Copyright © 2024 All Rights Reserved.
